WJZ-TV Collection R0129.WJZ R0129.WJZ
Stage
- Evening Magazine, 1977-1991; EVMAG; 8 Reels 2 inch videotape: Quad; 4,676 Cassettes
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-06-18-1979-06-19; WJZ-EVMAG-040-001 (Mixed materials 40, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-06-19; WJZ-EVMAG-040-002 (Mixed materials 40, Tape 2)
    - Werner Erhard & Est., 1979-06-19; WJZ_EVMAG-040-002-02 (Mixed materials 40, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-06-20-1979-06-21; WJZ-EVMAG-040-003 (Mixed materials 40, Tape 3)
    - Bob Smith, 1979-06-20; WJZ-EVMAG-040-003-01 (Mixed materials 40, Tape 3, Segment 1)
    - Best Buys, 1979-06-21; WJZ-EVMAG-040-003-02 (Mixed materials 40, Tape 3, Segment 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-06-20; WJZ-EVMAG-040-004 (Mixed materials 40, Tape 4)
    - Andrew's Wyeth's Sister, 1979-06-20; WJZ-EVMAG-040-004-01 (Mixed materials 40, Tape 4, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-06-21; WJZ-EVMAG-040-005 (Mixed materials 40, Tape 5)
    - Sky Writing, 1979-06-21; WJZ-EVMAG-040-005-01 (Mixed materials 40, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-06-22; WJZ-EVMAG-040-006 (Mixed materials 40, Tape 6)
    - Pet Show At Kennedy's, 1979-06-22; WJZ-EVMAG-040-006-01 (Mixed materials 40, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-05; WJZ-EVMAG-041-001 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 1)
    - George Hamilton, 1979-07-05; WJZ-EVMAG-041-001-01 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 1, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-06; WJZ-EVMAG-041-002 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 2)
    - Baltimore's Bunny, 1979-07-06; WJZ-EVMAG-041-002-01 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-06-1979-07-09; WJZ-EVMAG-041-003 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-09; WJZ-EVMAG-041-004 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 4)
    - National Spelling Camps, 1979-07-09; WJZ-EVMAG-041-004-01 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 4, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-10; WJZ-EVMAG-041-005 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 5)
    - Dog Catcher, 1979-07-10; WJZ-EVMAG-041-005-01 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-10-1979-07-11; WJZ-EVMAG-041-006 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-041-007 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 7)
    - Cannes 1, 1979-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-041-007-01 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 7, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-041-008 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 8)
    - Cannes 2, 1979-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-041-008-01 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 8, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-041-009 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 9)
    - Cannes Film Festival, 1979-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-041-009-01 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 9, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-041-010 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 10)
    - Hydro Plane, 1979-07-12; WJZ-EVMAG-041-010-01 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 10, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-12-1979-07-13; WJZ-EVMAG-041-011 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-13; WJZ-EVMAG-041-012 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 12)
    - Cannes Film Festival 2, 1979-07-13; WJZ-EVMAG-041-012-01 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 12, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-16; WJZ-EVMAG-041-013 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 13)
    - Blue Angels, 1979-07-16; WJZ-EVMAG-041-013-01 (Mixed materials 41, Segment 13, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-16-1979-07-17; WJZ-EVMAG-041-014 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-17; WJZ-EVMAG-041-015 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 15)
    - Tomb Guards, 1979-07-17; WJZ-EVMAG-041-015-01 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 15, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-18-1979-07-19; WJZ-EVMAG-041-016 (Mixed materials 41, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-18; WJZ-EVMAG-042-001 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 1)
    - Work With 13,000 Volts, 1979-07-18; WJZ-EVMAG-042-001-01 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 1, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-19; WJZ-EVMAG-042-002 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 2)
    - Susan Anton, 1979-07-19; WJZ-EVMAG-042-002-01 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-20-1979-07-23; WJZ-EVMAG-042-003 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-23; WJZ-EVMAG-042-004 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 4)
    - Blaze Starr, 1979-07-23; WJZ-EVMAG-042-004-01 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 4, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-24-1979-07-25; WJZ-EVMAG-042-005 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-24; WJZ-EVMAG-042-006 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 6)
    - Wild Falcons, 1979-07-24; WJZ-EVMAG-042-006-01 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-25; WJZ-EVMAG-042-007 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 7)
    - Truck Drivers Race, 1979-07-25; WJZ-EVMAG-042-007-01 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 7, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-26; WJZ-EVMAG-042-008 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 8)
    - "Bionic" In Baltimore, 1979-07-25; WJZ-EVMAG-042-008-01 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 8, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-26-1979-07-27; WJZ-EVMAG-042-009 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-27; WJZ-EVMAG-042-010 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 10)
    - Noah's Ark In Maryland, 1979-07-27; WJZ-EVMAG-042-010-01
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-30-1979-07-31; WJZ-EVMAG-042-011 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-31; WJZ-EVMAG-042-012 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 12)
    - Big Band Sound, 1979-07-31; WJZ-EVMAG-042-012-01 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 12, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-07-31; WJZ-EVMAG-042-013 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 13)
    - Amityville Star/James Brolin, 1979-07-31; WJZ-EVMAG-042-013-01 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 13, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-01; WJZ-EVMAG-042-014 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 14)
    - Baltimore's Love Boat, 1979-08-01; WJZ-EVMAG-042-014-01 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 14, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-01-1979-08-02; WJZ-EVMAG-042-015 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-02; WJZ-EVMAG-042-016 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 16)
    - I Find Baseball's Superstars, 1979-08-02; WJZ-EVMAG-042-016-01 (Mixed materials 42, Tape 16, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-03-1979-08-06; WJZ-EVMAG-043-001 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-06; WJZ-EVMAG-043-002 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 2)
    - Olympic Horses That Dance, 1979-08-06; WJZ-EVMAG-042-002-01 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-07-1979-08-08; WJZ-EVMAG-043-003 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-09; WJZ-EVMAG-043-004 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 4)
    - Lady Paramedic, 1979-08-09; WJZ-EVMAG-043-004-01 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 4, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-10; WJZ-EVMAG-043-005 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 5)
    - Amish People, 1979-08-10; WJZ-EVMAG-043-005-01 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-09-1979-08-10; WJZ-EVMAG-043-006 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-13-1979-08-14; WJZ-EVMAG-043-007 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 7)
    - National Reel 604, 1979-08-14; WJZ-EVMAG-042-007-01 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 7, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-15-1979-08-16; WJZ-EVMAG-043-008 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 8)
    - Dogs For The Deaf, 1979-08-15; WJZ-EVMAG-043-008-01 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 8, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-17-1979-08-20; WJZ-EVMAG-043-009 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-21-1979-08-22; WJZ-EVMAG-043-010 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-23; WJZ-EVMAG-043-011 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 11)
    - Earl Weaver, 1979-08-23; WJZ-EVMAG-043-011-01 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 11, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-23-1979-09-07; WJZ-EVMAG-043-012 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-23-1979-08-24; WJZ-EVMAG-043-013 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-27-1979-08-28; WJZ-EVMAG-043-014 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-27-1979-09-03; WJZ-EVMAG-043-015 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-29; WJZ-EVMAG-043-016 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 16)
    - Knights in Baltimore, 1979-08-29; WJZ-EVMAG-043-016-01 (Mixed materials 43, Tape 16, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-29-1979-08-30; WJZ-EVMAG-044-001 (Mixed materials 44, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-08-31; WJZ-EVMAG-044-002 (Mixed materials 44, Tape 2)
    - 300 MPH Fall, 1979-08-31; WJZ-EVMAG-044-002-01 (Mixed materials 44, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-02; WJZ-EVMAG-044-003 (Mixed materials 44, Tape 3)
    - Sally Field 1of 2, 1979-09-02; WJZ-EVMAG-044-003-01 (Mixed materials 44, Tape 3, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-13; WJZ-EVMAG-045-001 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 1)
    - Emergency Room Doctors At Play Shock Trauma, 1979-09-13; WJZ-EVMAG-045-001-01 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 1, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-14; WJZ-EVMAG-045-002 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 2)
    - Dive 180 FT. Into Inner Harbor, 1979-09-14; WJZ-EVMAG-045-002-01 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-14-1979-09-17; WJZ-EVMAG-045-003 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 3)
    - Special Olympics, 1979-09-14; WJZ-EVMAG-045-003-01 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 3, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-14-1979-09-19; WJZ-EVMAG-045-004 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-17; WJZ-EVMAG-045-005 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 5)
    - Special Olympics Star 1, 1979-09-17; WJZ-EVMAG-045-005-01 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-18; WJZ-EVMAG-045-006 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 6)
    - Special Olympics Star 2, 1979-09-18; WJZ-EVMAG-045-006-01 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-18-1979-09-19; WJZ-EVMAG-045-007 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-19; WJZ-EVMAG-045-008 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 8)
    - Greatest Softball Team, 1979-09-19; WJZ-EVMAG-045-008-01 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 8, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-20; WJZ-EVMAG-045-009 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 9)
    - Street Vendors: Baltimore, 1979-09-20; WJZ-EVMAG-045-009-01 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 9, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-20-1979-09-21; WJZ-EVMAG-045-010 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-20-1979-09-25; WJZ-EVMAG-045-011 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-21; WJZ-EVMAG-045-012 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 12)
    - Waterskiing No Shoes, 1979-09-21; WJZ-EVMAG-045-012-01 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 12, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-24; WJZ-EVMAG-045-013 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 13)
    - Aerobic Dance Craze, 1979-09-24; WJZ-EVMAG-045-013-01 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 13, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-24-1979-09-25; WJZ-EVMAG-045-014 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-25; WJZ-EVMAG-045-015 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 15)
    - Play Baseball Better That Boys, 1979-09-25; WJZ-EVMAG-045-015-01 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 15, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-26-1979-09-27; WJZ-EVMAG-045-016 (Mixed materials 45, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-26-1979-10-01; WJZ-EVMAG-046-001 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-27; WJZ-EVMAG-046-002 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 2)
    - I Hunt Bats, 1979-09-27; WJZ-EVMAG-046-002-01 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 2, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-28; WJZ-EVMAG-046-003 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 3)
    - (1) Gary Coleman, 1979-09-28; WJZ-EVMAG-046-003-01 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 3, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-28; WJZ-EVMAG-046-004 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 4)
    - Gary Coleman, 1979-09-28; WJZ-EVMAG-046-004-01 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 4, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-29; WJZ-EVMAG-046-005 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 5)
    - Lady Pool Shark, 1979-09-29; WJZ-EVMAG-046-005-01 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-09-28-1979-10-01; WJZ-EVMAG-046-006 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-01; WJZ-EVMAG-046-007 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 7)
    - Chesapeake Bay Monster?, 1979-10-01; WJZ-EVMAG-046-007-01 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 7, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-02; WJZ-EVMAG-046-008 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 8)
    - Nudist Camp, 1979-10-02; WJZ-EVMAG-046-008-01 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 8, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-10; WJZ-EVMAG-046-009 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 9)
    - TV Commercials, 1979-10-10; WJZ-EVMAG-046-009-01 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 9, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-11; WJZ-EVMAG-046-010 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 10)
    - Best Harmonica Player, 1979-10-11; WJZ-EVMAG-046-010-01 (Mixed materials 46, Tape 10, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-05; WJZ-EVMAG-047-001 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 1)
    - Behind Miss America Pageant, 1979-10-05; WJZ-EVMAG-047-001-01 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 1, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-08-1979-10-09; WJZ-EVMAG-047-002 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-09; WJZ-EVMAG-047-003 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 3)
    - Stripper For God, 1979-10-09; WJZ-EVMAG-047-003-01 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 3, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-09-1979-10-15; WJZ-EVMAG-047-004 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-12; WJZ-EVMAG-047-005 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 5)
    - Demolition Derby, 1979-10-12; WJZ-EVMAG-047-005-01 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 5, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-12; WJZ-EVMAG-047-006 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 6)
    - James Cleveland, 1979-10-12; WJZ-EVMAG-047-006-01 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 6, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-12-1979-10-15; WJZ-EVMAG-047-007 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-15; WJZ-EVMAG-047-008 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 8)
    - Gas Station For Super ships, 1979-10-15; WJZ-EVMAG-047-008-01 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 8, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-16; WJZ-EVMAG-047-009 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 9)
    - Martin Sheen, 1979-10-16; WJZ-EVMAG-047-009-01 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 9, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-16-1979-10-17; WJZ-EVMAG-047-010 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-16-1979-10-23; WJZ-EVMAG-047-011 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-18; WJZ-EVMAG-047-012 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 12)
    - Baltimore Muppets, 1979-10-18; WJZ-EVMAG-047-012-01 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 12, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-19; WJZ-EVMAG-047-013 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 13)
    - Most Beautiful Bodies, 1979-10-19; WJZ-EVMAG-047-013-01 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 13, Segment 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-22-1979-10-23; WJZ-EVMAG-047-014 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-23; WJZ-EVMAG-047-015 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-24; WJZ-EVMAG-047-016 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-24-1979-10-29; WJZ-EVMAG-047-017 (Mixed materials 47, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-24; WJZ-EVMAG-048-001 (Mixed materials 48, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-23; WJZ-EVMAG-048-002 (Mixed materials 48, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-24; WJZ-EVMAG-048-003 (Mixed materials 48, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-25; WJZ-EVMAG-048-004 (Mixed materials 48, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-25-1979-10-26; WJZ-EVMAG-048-005 (Mixed materials 48, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-10-26; WJZ-EVMAG-048-006 (Mixed materials 48, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-11-06-1979-11-07; WJZ-EVMAG-049-001 (Mixed materials 49, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-11-08; WJZ-EVMAG-049-002 (Mixed materials 49, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-11-07; WJZ-EVMAG-049-003 (Mixed materials 49, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-11-08-1979-11-09; WJZ-EVMAG-049-004 (Mixed materials 49, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-11-20; WJZ-EVMAG-050-001 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-11-21; WJZ-EVMAG-050-002 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-11-23; WJZ-EVMAG-050-003 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-11-26; WJZ-EVMAG-050-004 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-11-27; WJZ-EVMAG-050-005 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-11-29-1979-11-30; WJZ-EVMAG-050-006 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-11-27-1979-12-04; WJZ-EVMAG-050-007 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-11-28; WJZ-EVMAG-050-008 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-05; WJZ-EVMAG-050-009 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-05; WJZ-EVMAG-050-010 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-04; WJZ-EVMAG-050-011 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-05-1979-12-06; WJZ-EVMAG-050-012 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-06; WJZ-EVMAG-050-013 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-07-1979-12-12; WJZ-EVMAG-050-014 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-07-1979-12-10; WJZ-EVMAG-050-015 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-10; WJZ-EVMAG-050-016 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-12-1979-12-13; WJZ-EVMAG-050-017 (Mixed materials 50, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-13; WJZ-EVMAG-051-001 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-14; WJZ-EVMAG-051-002 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-14-1979-12-19; WJZ-EVMAG-051-003 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-14-1979-12-17; WJZ-EVMAG-051-004 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-15-1979-12-18; WJZ-EVMAG-051-005 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-18-1979-12-19; WJZ-EVMAG-051-006 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-19; WJZ-EVMAG-051-007 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-20-1979-12-21; WJZ-EVMAG-051-008 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-21; WJZ-EVMAG-051-009 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-22; WJZ-EVMAG-051-010 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-24; WJZ-EVMAG-051-011 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-24-1979-12-25; WJZ-EVMAG-051-012 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-26-1979-12-27; WJZ-EVMAG-051-013 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-27; WJZ-EVMAG-051-014 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-27; WJZ-EVMAG-051-015 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-18-1979-12-31; WJZ-EVMAG-051-016 (Mixed materials 51, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980; WJZ-EVMAG-052--005 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980; WJZ-EVMAG-052--006 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980; WJZ-EVMAG-052--007 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980; WJZ-EVMAG-052--008 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-31; WJZ-EVMAG-052-001 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-31; WJZ-EVMAG-052-002 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-31; WJZ-EVMAG-052-003 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1979-12-31; WJZ-EVMAG-052-004 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-01-1980-01-02; WJZ-EVMAG-052-009 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-02; WJZ-EVMAG-052-010 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-03; WJZ-EVMAG-052-011 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-03-1980-01-04; WJZ-EVMAG-052-012 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-07-1980-01-08; WJZ-EVMAG-052-013 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-08; WJZ-EVMAG-052-014 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-09-1980-01-10; WJZ-EVMAG-052-015 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-10; WJZ-EVMAG-052-016 (Mixed materials 52, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-10; WJZ-EVMAG-053-001 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-11-1980-01-14; WJZ-EVMAG-053-002 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-11; WJZ-EVMAG-053-003 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-14; WJZ-EVMAG-053-004 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-15; WJZ-EVMAG-053-005 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-16; WJZ-EVMAG-053-006 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-15-1980-01-16; WJZ-EVMAG-053-007 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-17; WJZ-EVMAG-053-008 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-17-1980-01-18; WJZ-EVMAG-053-009 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-18; WJZ-EVMAG-053-010 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-18; WJZ-EVMAG-053-011 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-18-1980-01-25; WJZ-EVMAG-053-012 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-21; WJZ-EVMAG-053-013 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-19; WJZ-EVMAG-053-014 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-23; WJZ-EVMAG-053-015 (Mixed materials 53, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-23; WJZ-EVMAG-054-001 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-23; WJZ-EVMAG-054-002 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-23-1980-02-24; WJZ-EVMAG-054-003 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-24; WJZ-EVMAG-054-004 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-23-1980-02-01; WJZ-EVMAG-054-005 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-25; WJZ-EVMAG-054-006 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-25; WJZ-EVMAG-054-007 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-25-1980-01-28; WJZ-EVMAG-054-008 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-28-1980-02-04; WJZ-EVMAG-054-009 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-28; WJZ-EVMAG-054-010 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-29; WJZ-EVMAG-054-011 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-29-1980-01-30; WJZ-EVMAG-054-012 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-30; WJZ-EVMAG-054-013 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-31; WJZ-EVMAG-054-014 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-01-31-1980-02-01; WJZ-EVMAG-054-015 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 15)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-04; WJZ-EVMAG-054-016 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 16)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-04; WJZ-EVMAG-054-017 (Mixed materials 54, Tape 17)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-04-1980-02-05; WJZ-EVMAG-055-001 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 1)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-04; WJZ-EVMAG-055-002 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 2)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-05-1980-02-08; WJZ-EVMAG-055-003 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 3)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-06; WJZ-EVMAG-055-004 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 4)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-06-1980-02-07; WJZ-EVMAG-055-005 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 5)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-07; WJZ-EVMAG-055-006 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 6)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-08; WJZ-EVMAG-055-007 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 7)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-11-1980-02-12; WJZ-EVMAG-055-008 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 8)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-11-1980-02-15; WJZ-EVMAG-055-009 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 9)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-13-1980-02-14; WJZ-EVMAG-055-010 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 10)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-14; WJZ-EVMAG-055-011 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 11)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-14-1980-02-22; WJZ-EVMAG-055-012 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 12)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-15; WJZ-EVMAG-055-013 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 13)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-15-1980-02-18; WJZ-EVMAG-055-014 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 14)
  - Evening Magazine, 1980-02-19; WJZ-EVMAG-055-015 (Mixed materials 55, Tape 15)